{
    "subject": "Ferdinand_II_of_the_Two_Sicilies",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Maria_Christina_of_Savoy",
    "human_readable": "Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies is married to Maria Christina of Savoy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9681274890899658,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies and Maria Christina of Savoy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9663653373718262,
            "question": "What is the historical context of Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies and Maria Christina of Savoy's marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9570704698562622,
            "question": "Who is Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9555463790893555,
            "question": "To whom was Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9082706570625305,
            "question": "Who was Maria Christina of Savoy married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9081783294677734,
            "question": "What was the name of Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies' wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8902013897895813,
            "question": "What is the name of Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies' spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8528193235397339,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.805853545665741,
            "question": "Was Maria Christina of Savoy married to a king?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5475999116897583,
            "question": "Is Maria Christina of Savoy related to any other royal families?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies is married to Maria Christina of Savoy.",
            "html": "yago_28625_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Maria Christina of Savoy married to a king?",
            "html": "yago_28625_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the marriage of Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies?",
            "html": "yago_28625_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies' spouse?",
            "html": "yago_28625_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28625_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that on November 21, 1832, Maria Cristina of Savoy married Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies. Therefore, the statement that Ferdinand II of the Two Sicilies is married to Maria Christina of Savoy is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}